Personal Information_____

Lee Jenn Wah

No 1, Jalan BSJ 2, Taman Bukit Segar Jaya, 43200 Batu 9 Cheras Selangor jaywah2008@hotmail.com I/C: 971217-56-5259

I/C: 9/1217-56-525 H.P: 016-2856899





Graduated First Class from University, experienced 9 months of **practical Software Engineering experience** at **Kaodim** and **Grab** as of now. Now, I am looking forward to management trainee programme where I can involve in more business side of career.

Personal Website: https://jennwah.github.io/

Working Experience_____

Software Engineer, Full-Stack at Grab (Feb 2021 – current)

- Work closely with a team of 3 engineers, 1 Lead Product Manager and 1 Software Engineering Manager to deliver product changes through writing codes and Software Engineering implementation
- Implement new features on product as per business requirement in growing product.
- Scrum meeting on daily basis to sync with team's progress. Utilize on platform such as JIRA to keep track of priorities and tasks.
- Practice Continuous Integration(CI)/Continuous Delivery(CD) to deploy changes to staging/production
- Main tech stack: ReactJs + Redux (frontend), Golang with gRPC (backend), AWS infrastructure services (EC2, S3, Lamda, DynamDB etc).
- Datadog Monitoring Tools
- Kibana logging tools
- Oncall rotation duties shift

Software Engineering Internship (Backend) at Kaodim (Oct 2021 – Dec 2021)

- **Ruby on Rails** backend tech stack
- Experienced full SDLC (software development life cycle) and Agile methodology in carrying out change requests (CR)/ fixing production bugs. Also practiced working on Kanban methodology such as using tools like Jira for project tracking management and Scrum, as to meeting up daily to discuss about pending/to-do/completed tasks
- Helped Kaodim in solving 20+ Change Requests (CR) and fixing production bugs. Involved in new features implementation as well.
- Practiced Object Oriented Programming and building reusable code and libraries for future use
- Experienced writing **unit tests** for every lines of code integrated in **Rspec** framework
- Collaborated with different stakeholders, eg Product Managers, QA teams and front-end teams to work on features implementation together.
- Experienced with different famous **Ruby gems:** eg, Mutations, Serializers, Sidekiq, Apartment, aasm, Capistrano (for deployment)
- Proficient git and github knowledge, practiced code reviews and continuous integration (CI). At Kaodim, we run automated CI tests on CircleCi.

Programming projects_

MERN full-stack social web app

Full-stack social app with MERN stack technology. Features include:

- Authentication and Authorization (users register, log in, sign out with JsonWebToken and bcrypt for password hashing)
- User create post with text and photo, delete their post
- User can follow or unfollow other users. User also get suggestion for following other users in the social platform
- User can like or dislike posts. User can comment on posts.
- User can bookmark other posts to be saved into their collection.
- Load more button feature to load more posts each time user click at home page. To improve web's optimization and scalability.

Github repository: https://github.com/jennwah/mern-social-app

Chat web application

A full-stack chat application using MERN stack with Redux implementation as well. Socket.io is used for real-time functionality. A basic full-stack chat application project on https://github.com/jennwah/mern-chat-socketio

Simon Game

A Javascript and Jquery game project where it tests a player's memory. Players have to remember the sequence of lights shown as each levels passes, sequence got more and more complex. https://github.com/jennwah/SimonGame

React Project – Covid-19 statistics tracker

A simple react project where data is fetched from API calling and rendered in front end. React Hooks are used. Design with Material UI. https://github.com/jennwah/react-project-covid19-stats-tracker

Education and Academic Achievements_____

University of Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR) Sungai Long campus

Bachelor of Science (HONS) Actuarial Science

Graduated Honors Degree with Distinction (First Class), with CGPA 3.77

Achievements: 3 Dean Lists' Awards and 3 President List's Awards

MUET standard: Band 5

Methodist College Kuala Lumpur

Cambridge GCE A-levels

 $\label{eq:Achievements} A chievements: Graduated with Mathematics (A* grade), \ Physics(A* grade), \ Further Mathematics (A grade), \ Economics (A grade)$

Methodist Boys' Secondary Kuala Lumpur

SPM (Sijil Peperiksaan Malaysia) Achievements: **8A+, 1A, 2A-**

Skills and Personal Qualities_____

- Willing to learn and adapt to fast-paced environment
- Particularly in favor of helping start-ups to grow as I am a start-up inspired kind of guy too ©
- Take ownership in every tasks I own. Take responsibility of every code changes.
- Challenge seeker

- Technology Enthusiast
- Sports Enthusiast (Love Badminton & Futsal ©)
- Microsoft Office: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint

Extra-curricular Activities_____

April 2019	Elected as person in-charge of Publicity Department for UTAR Zero Waste Awareness
_	Campaign Committee
Oct 2017	Student Exchange Program to University of Economics, Ho Chi Minh City
2015-2016	Community Service in Calvary Land Organisation Homes through College's Service
	Learning
April 2016	Awarded Silver Medal in 2 nd Beaver Computational Thinking Competition (Student
-	Category)
May 2014	Represented my high school to participate in Sunway College A-level Maths & Logic
	Challenge (State Level)
July 2011	Participated in UKECharisma Project Health Awareness
2010 - 2011	Awarded 3 medals in Annual Sport events

Language Proficiency_____

- Written: English (Fluent), Chinese (Fluent) and Malay (Proficient)
- Spoken: English (Fluent), Chinese (Fluent) and Malay (Average)

Additional Information_____

• Current leave notice: 2 months